Guide to the Associate University Librarian for Technical Services, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Integrated Technical Services and Systems records of Donald Waters, 1986-1994; Accession 1995-A-067a
  - Computer files, 412 (Box 8–13)
    - Recovered Disk, Angela's Capstone Conf., Sept. 7-8, -Peron Paper, 1995-a-067-0367; 1 (Box 13)
    - Ponpo, Sem List, To Test Mailing, 1995-a-067-0368; 1 (Box 13)
    - Test Mailing to WP List, 1995-a-067-0369; 1 (Box 13)
    - Working Papers/CNG's 2, 1995-a-067-0370; 1 (Box 13)
    - Working Papers/CNG's, 1995-a-067-0371; 1 (Box 13)
    - Download Files Misc., 1995-a-067-0372; 1 (Box 13)
    - Aspen Interim Report, Atlantic bud2, 1995-a-067-0373; 1 (Box 13)
    - Ford Grant Acctg. Nov. 98 -> Present, Aspen Grant Acctg. May '98 -> Present, 1995-a-067-0374; 1 (Box 13)
    - Kellogg, 1998 Financial Report, 1999 Financial Report, 1995-a-067-0375; 1 (Box 13)
    - Lilly Polity, Jan 99 - July 99, 1995-a-067-0376; 1 (Box 13)
    - Lilly Leadership, -Report for 9/98-6/99, 1995-a-067-0377; 1 (Box 13)
    - Kellogg/Grant Acct., Kellogg '98 End-of-Yr Report, 1995-a-067-0378; 1 (Box 13)
    - Kellogg Grant Acctg. (2000), 1995-a-067-0379; 1 (Box 13)
    - Lilly Polity '99, Financial Report, 1995-a-067-0380; 1 (Box 13)
    - Backup Folder - Grant, Accounting, 1995-a-067-0381; 1 (Box 13)
    - Disk #2, Backup, -Grant Acct 4/99, 1995-a-067-0382; 1 (Box 13)
    - Lilly Polity Proposal, 1995-a-067-0383; 1 (Box 13)
    - Telephone, Meetings, e-mail, conference - 20 years, 1995-a-067-0384; 1 (Box 13)
    - Publication List Update, (All Files) 1991, 1995-a-067-0385; 1 (Box 13)
    - Annual Reports - KR, 1995-a-067-0386; 1 (Box 13)
    - Annual Reports, 1995-a-067-0387; 1 (Box 13)
    - Review Copy Requests, Book Orders, Peter Hall Messages, 1995-a-067-0388; 1 (Box 13)
    - Budget May 01, 1995-a-067-0389; 1 (Box 13)
    - Barsade Case, 1995-a-067-0390; 1 (Box 13)
    - Backup C-Files, A-File 0024, 1995-a-067-0391; 1 (Box 13)
    - Religion Project - Back Up, 1995-a-067-0392; 1 (Box 13)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0393; 1 (Box 13)
    - Backup, C: Files, Fleishman - WPCVR, 1995-a-067-0394; 1 (Box 13)
    - Ponpo-Proposal, Letters - BHG, Kellogg - Proposal, Kaiser - Proposal, 1995-a-067-0395; 1 (Box 13)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0396; 1 (Box 13)
    - Miriam M. Wood, Cases in Nonprofit Governance, Microsoft Word J.1, 1995-a-067-0397; 1 (Box 13)
    - CGP Files:, Proposals, Letters, Reports, 1995-a-067-0398; 1 (Box 13)
    - CGP Files:, Proposals, Letters, Etc., 1995-a-067-0399; 1 (Box 13)
    - CGP - Old Versions, 1995-a-067-0400; 1 (Box 13)
    - C:\wp50\wpf\gray, #1, 1995-a-067-0401; 1 (Box 13)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0402; 1 (Box 13)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0403; 1 (Box 13)
    - Back-up, Gray2.wp, Gray4.wp, Gray3.wp, 1995-a-067-0404; 1 (Box 13)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0405; 1 (Box 13)
    - 3-12-90 Back-Up, 1995-a-067-0406; 1 (Box 13)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0407; 1 (Box 13)
    - Ponpo Seminars, 1995-a-067-0408; 1 (Box 13)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0409; 1 (Box 13)
    - Research Reports, 1995-a-067-0410; 1 (Box 13)
    - Ponpo Proposal, 1995-a-067-0411; 1 (Box 13)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0412; 1 (Box 13)
- Correspondence files of AUL Gerald Lowell, 1986-1993; Accession 1996-A-060
  - Letters received, 1986-1992 (Box 1)
  - Memos sent, 1988-1993 (Box 1)
  - Memos received, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Memos sent, 1986-1993 (Box 2)
  - Memos received, 1988-1992 (Box 3)
  - Reorganization Council meetings (Box 4)
  - System Automation Memo (SAM) (Box 4)
  - Technical Services Staff - job satisfaction survey (Box 4)
- Records of Ake Koel as head of technical services, circa 1980-1989; Accession 1997-A-001
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2024
  - Acquisitions Department
    - Book Sales (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Budget and Funds (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Dealers (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Forms (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Fund Register (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Gifts and Exchanges (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - PL 480 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Staff (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Statistics (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - African Collection (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American National Standards Institute (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - American Oriental Society (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Association of Research Libraries (ARL) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Art and Architecture Library (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Art Cataloging Team (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Arts of the Book Collection (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bibliography Department (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - British Library (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bro-dart, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Brown University (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Business Manager's Office (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Card Processing (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Carrollton Press (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Catalogue Department
    - Forms (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Organization (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Output (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Staff (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Catalogues
    - Card (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - C.O.M. (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Expansion (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Shelf List (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Shelf List - Filming (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Signs and Guides (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Circulation Department (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Council on Library Resources (CLR) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Collection Development (Standing Advisory Committee) (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Colorado State University (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Columbia University (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Committee on Archive Tape Processing (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Computers and Computing (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Conser Project (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Conservation Division (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Staff (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Copyright (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Cornell University (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Questionnaires., Surveys (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Center for Research Libraries (CRL) (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Cross Campus Library (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Dartmouth College (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Dissertations (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Divinity Library (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Duke University (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - East Asian Collection (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Economic Growth Center Library (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health Library (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - ESTC/NA (18th Century Short Title Catalog/NA) (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Filing Rules (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Department Libraries (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Filing Unit (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Staff (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Flex Time (Flexible Scheduling) (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - GEAC (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - General Bookbinding Company (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Georgetown University (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Government Publications (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Harvard University (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - HEW (Department of Health, Education and Welfare) (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Historical Sound Recordings (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Indiana University (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Interlibrary Loan (ILL) (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - International Federation of Documentation (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - ISBN (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Johns Hopkins University (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Kline Science Library (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Latin American Collection (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Law Library (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - LC (Library of Congress)
    - AACR (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Authority Records (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Automation Networking etc. (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Cards (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Catalogs (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - CIP (Cataloging in Publication) (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Classification (Box 3, Folder 86)
      - Other Libraries (Box 3, Folder 87)
      - Yale (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Collection Development (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - COMARC (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Depository Catalog (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Filing Rules (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - MARC (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - NPAC (Box 3, Folder 95)
      - Processing Department (Box 3, Folder 96)
      - Progress Report (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - National Union Catalog (NUC) (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Serials (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Service Proposals (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Source Catalog Division (Box 3, Folder 101)
      - Staff (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Subject Lists (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Lewis Walpole Library (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Librarian's Annual Report (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Statistics (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Librarian's Conference (Box 3, Folder 107 - 108)
  - Library Staff Association (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Literature Cataloging Team (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - MandPSA News Notes (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Mail Service (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Manuscripts and Archives (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Map Collection (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - MATPS (Machine Aided Technical Processing System) (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Development (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - MATPS (second folder) (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Medical Library (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Cataloging Division (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Microtexts (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Cataloging (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Music Library (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Name Authority Unit (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - National Commission on Libraries and Information Science (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Near East Cataloging Division (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - Output (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Staff (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - New Haven Colony Historical Society (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - New Have Public Library (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - New York Public Library (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - New York University (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Newspapers (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Northwestern University, Evanston, IL (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - OCLC
    - Annual Report (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Cataloging (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Hardware (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Orientation Committee - Including Orientation (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Pamphlets (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Pennsylvania State University (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Performance Evaluation (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Personnel Office (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Philosophy and Religion Cataloging Team (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Photographic Services (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Studio (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Preparations Division (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Commercial Binding (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Plating and Marking (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Staff (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Preservation Department (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Staff (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Preservation Division (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Staff (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Princeton University (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Public Services (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Random House, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Rare Book Cataloging Division (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - Output (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Staff (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Record Processing and Maintenance Division (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Staff (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Reference Department (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Research Libraries Group, Inc. (RLG)
    - AandA Task Force (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Acquisitions Subsystem (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Africa Special Interest Group (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Agreement with Infour (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Authorities Subsystem (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - BIBPAC - 76/0001 (Box 5, Folder 168)
      - BCSDF (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - BIBTECH (Box 5, Folder 170)
      - Minutes (September 17, 1979) (Box 5, Folder 171)
      - Standing Committee on Serials (Box 5, Folder 172)
      - Steering Committee (Box 5, Folder 173)
        - Minutes (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - Board of Governors (Box 5, Folder 175)
      - Systems Committee (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - Budget (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - Bylaws (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - Cataloging (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - Cataloging Policy Control Subcommittee
      - Shared (Box 5, Folder 180)
        - Cooperative Cataloging of Microfilm Sets (Box 5, Folder 181)
        - Monographs in Series (Box 5, Folder 182)
      - Standards (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - Collection Development Task Force (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - Communication (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - Communications Subsystems (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - Conspectus (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - Copyright (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - Costs
      - Estimates and Budgets (Box 5, Folder 189)
      - Invoices (Box 5, Folder 190)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 191)
      - Rate Schedules (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - Database - Loading (Box 6, Folder 193)
      - Reconfiguration (Box 6, Folder 194)
      - Special Files (Box 6, Folder 195)
    - Development - Archives and MSS (Box 6, Folder 196)
      - Authority Control (Box 6, Folder 197)
      - Briefings (Box 6, Folder 198)
      - Carnegie Study (Box 6, Folder 199)
      - Linked Local Systems (Box 6, Folder 200)
      - Non-Roman Alphabets (Box 6, Folder 201)
      - Patron Access (Box 6, Folder 202)
      - Schedules (Box 6, Folder 203)
    - Document Control System (Box 6, Folder 204)
    - East European Special Interest Group (Box 6, Folder 205)
    - EXEC 77/0001 (Box 6, Folder 206)
    - Government Documents Special Interest Group (Box 6, Folder 207)
    - Hardware (Box 6, Folder 208)
      - Installation (Box 6, Folder 209)
      - Printers (Box 6, Folder 210)
      - Terminals (Box 6, Folder 211)
    - ILL (Box 6, Folder 212)
    - Informal Committee of Systems Personnel (Box 6, Folder 213)
    - Interest Groups (Box 6, Folder 214)
    - Law Library Committee (Box 6, Folder 215)
    - Law Task Force (Box 6, Folder 216)
    - Medical/Health Services Program (Box 6, Folder 217)
    - Membership (Box 6, Folder 218)
    - Membership and Services Task Force (Box 6, Folder 219)
    - Miscellanea (Box 6, Folder 220)
    - Mission and Goals (Box 6, Folder 221)
    - Organization (Box 6, Folder 222)
    - Preservation (Box 6, Folder 223)
    - Preservation Committee (Box 6, Folder 224)
    - Products - Archive Tapes (Box 6, Folder 225)
      - Cards (Box 6, Folder 226)
      - COM Catalogs (Box 6, Folder 227)
    - Program Committees (Box 6, Folder 228)
    - Public Service Committee (Box 6, Folder 229)
    - Reader Service Committee (Box 6, Folder 230)
    - RLIN
      - Agreement (Box 7, Folder 231)
      - LC (NUC Reporting) (Box 7, Folder 232)
      - Manuals, Training Aids, etc. (Box 7, Folder 233)
      - Operations Update (Box 7, Folder 234)
      - Organization (Box 7, Folder 235)
      - Report System (Box 7, Folder 236)
      - Service Schedules, System Performance, etc. (Box 7, Folder 237)
      - Yale Coordinator (Box 7, Folder 238)
    - Serials Task Force (Box 7, Folder 239)
    - Slavic Special Interest Group (Box 7, Folder 240)
    - Space Task Force (Box 7, Folder 241)
    - Software (Box 7, Folder 242)
    - STAC - Subcommittee on Acquisition of OCLC Arch. Tape (Box 7, Folder 243)
      - Subcommittee on Materials Processing (Box 7, Folder 244)
      - Subcommittees (Box 7, Folder 245)
    - Standards - AACR2
      - AMC (Box 7, Folder 246)
      - Cataloging - BLC (Box 7, Folder 247)
        - Microform (Box 7, Folder 248)
        - Monos (Box 7, Folder 249)
        - MRDF (Box 7, Folder 250)
        - Serials (Box 7, Folder 251)
      - RLIN (Box 7, Folder 252)
      - Error Reports (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - STF 75/0001 (Box 7, Folder 254)
    - SYS 75/0001 (Box 8, Folder 255)
    - Task Force on Cooperative Cataloging and Shared Access (Box 8, Folder 256)
    - Task Force on the Automated Bibliographic Control System (Box 8, Folder 257)
    - Use - Command Logs
      - Other than Technical Service (Box 8, Folder 258)
      - RLG Members, Organization, Searching, etc. (Box 8, Folder 259)
      - RLIN Statistics
        - 1983
        - 1985 (Box 8, Folder 260)
    - Users (Box 8, Folder 261)
    - Yale Coordinator
      - Liaison (Box 8, Folder 262)
      - Systems Office (Box 8, Folder 263)
      - YULC (Box 8, Folder 264)
  - Research Publications Inc. (Box 8, Folder 265)
  - Retirements (Box 8, Folder 266)
  - Retreats (Box 8, Folder 267)
  - Romanization (Box 8, Folder 268)
  - Rutgers - The State University (Box 8, Folder 269)
  - Safety (Box 8, Folder 270)
  - Sarason Report (Box 8, Folder 271)
  - Science Cataloging Team (Box 8, Folder 273)
  - Searching Division (Box 8, Folder 274)
  - Security (Box 8, Folder 275)
  - Seeley Mudd Library (Box 8, Folder 276)
  - Serials (Box 8, Folder 277)
  - Serials Cataloging Division
    - Output (Box 8, Folder 278)
    - Staff (Box 8, Folder 279)
  - Sick Leave (Box 8, Folder 280)
  - Slavic and East European Languages Division (Box 8, Folder 281)
    - Output (Box 8, Folder 282)
  - Social Science Library (Box 8, Folder 283)
  - Social Science Cataloging Team (Box 8, Folder 284)
  - Southeast Asia Collection (Box 8, Folder 285)
  - Southern Connecticut State University (Box 9, Folder 286)
  - Staff Development (Box 9, Folder 287)
  - Staff Forums (Box 9, Folder 288)
  - Standing Advisory Committee on Personnel (Box 9, Folder 289)
  - Stanford University (Box 9, Folder 290)
  - Student Employment (Box 9, Folder 291)
  - Summer Employment (Box 9, Folder 292)
  - Syracuse University (Box 9, Folder 293)
  - Systems Office (Box 9, Folder 294)
  - Task Force on Professional Staff Utilization (Box 9, Folder 295)
  - Technical Services
    - Annual Report (Box 9, Folder 296)
  - Telephone Use, Directories (Box 9, Folder 297)
  - TIAA/CREF Annuity Plan (Box 9, Folder 298)
  - Tibetan Collection (Box 9, Folder 299)
  - Travel (Box 9, Folder 300)
  - Union (Local 34 of here) (Box 9, Folder 301)
  - Union Contract
    - Compensation Administration (Box 9, Folder 302)
    - Stewards (Box 9, Folder 303)
  - United Way (Box 9, Folder 304)
  - University of British Columbia (Box 9, Folder 305)
  - University of California at Berkeley (Box 9, Folder 306)
  - University of California at Los Angeles (Box 9, Folder 307)
  - University of Chicago (Box 9, Folder 308)
  - University of Connecticut (Box 9, Folder 309)
  - University of Denver (Box 9, Folder 310)
  - University of Michigan (Box 9, Folder 311)
  - University of Minnesota (Box 9, Folder 312)
  - University of Toronto (Box 9, Folder 313)
  - University of Wisconsin (Box 9, Folder 314)
  - UTLAS (Box 9, Folder 315)
  - Visitors (Box 9, Folder 316)
  - Yale Center for British Art and Studies (Box 9, Folder 317)
  - Yale Computer Center (Box 9, Folder 318)
  - Yale Health Plan (Box 9, Folder 319)
  - Yale Library Association (Box 9, Folder 320)
  - Yale University
    - Administration - Data Services (Box 9, Folder 321)
    - Employee Benefits (Box 9, Folder 322)
    - Finances (Box 9, Folder 323)
    - Grants, Funds, etc. (Box 9, Folder 324)
  - Yale University Library
    - Memoranda (Box 9, Folder 325)
    - Organization (Box 9, Folder 326)
    - Space (Box 9, Folder 327)
  - Yale University Office of Public Information
    - Parking (Box 9, Folder 328)
    - Personnel (Box 9, Folder 329)
    - President (Box 9, Folder 330)
    - Press (Box 9, Folder 331)
    - Provost (Box 9, Folder 332)
    - Purchasing Department (Box 9, Folder 333)
    - University Operations (Box 9, Folder 334)
- Annual report input, 1984-1987; Accession 1997-A-020
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
  - Acquisitions department (SML), 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Acquisitions department (SML), G, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Acquisitions department (SML), S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Acquisition department, annual report, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administration (SML), Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - African collection (SML), S, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - African collection (SML), 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - African collection (SML), G, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Oriental Society (SML), Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - American Oriental Society (SML), S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Anthropology library, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Anthropology library, S, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Art and Architecture library, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Art and Architecture library, G, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Art and Architecture library, S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Arts of the Book collection (SML), including Bookplate collection, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Arts of the Book collection (SML), G; including Bookplate collection, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Arts of the Book collection (SML), S; including Bookplate collection, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Astronomy library, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Astronomy library, S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Babylonian collection (SML), Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Babylonian collection (SML), G, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Babylonian collection (SML), S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Beinecke Rare Book and MSS library, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Beinecke Rare Book and MSS library, G, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Beinecke Rare Book and MSS library, S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Bibliography department (SML), Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bibliography department (SML), G, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Business office (SML), including security, shipping, and receiving, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Business office (SML), G; including security, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Business office (SML), S; including security, shipping, and receiving, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Catalogue department (SML), Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Catalogue department (SML), G, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Catalogue department (SML), S, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Chemistry library, Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Chemistry library, S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Circulation department (SML), Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Circulation department (SML), G, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Circulation department (SML), S, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Classics library, Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Classics library, G, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Classics library, S, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Cowles Foundation library; G and S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Cross Campus library (SML), Undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Cross Campus library (SML), G, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Cross Campus library (SML), S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Divinity library, 1982-1987 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Divinity library, G, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Divinity library, S, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Drama library, Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Drama library, G, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Drama library, S, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - East Asia collection (SML), Undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - East Asia collection (SML), G, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - East Asia collection (SML), S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Economic Growth Center collection, Undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Economic Growth Center collection, S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Engineering and Applied Science library, Undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Engineering and Applied Science library, G, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Engineering and Applied Science library, S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health library, G and S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Franklin Papers (SML), G and S, Undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Geology library, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Geology library, G, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Geology library, S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Government documents' center, Undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Government documents' center, G, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Government documents' center, S, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Historical sound recordings collection (SML), Undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Historical sound recordings collection (SML), G, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Historical sound recordings collection (SML), S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Indological and Linguistic seminar library, G and S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 72)